#NowPlaying "LOOΠΔ/HeeJin - ViViD"
(LOOΠΔ performing each members' solo and unit's performances!)
#NowPlaying "LOOΠΔ/HeeJin&amp;HyunJin - I'll Be There"
#NowPlaying "LOOΠΔ 1/3 - Love&amp;Live"
Olivia Hye: (Hey~)
(LOOΠΔ TV PD accidentally turn off the light...)
Olivia Hye: Such a disaster~!
(Olivia Hye kindly solved the problem for LOOΠΔ TV PD!)
JinSoul: Hey~
Olivia Hye: PD took off the light by his back a little while ago~
Go Won: Like Olivia Hye~
Olivia Hye: Actually I made same mistake at a music show
(Olivia Hye made a same mistake like LOOΠΔ PD)
Olivia Hye: I was standing against the wall like this
Olivia Hye: However suddenly all the lights were turned off
Olivia Hye: Every singers and artists were there...
Olivia Hye: So... It was a kind of blackout made by me...
JinSoul: Today is 3 days before the debut concert...
JinSou: and also [Hi High] teaser was posted today~
Go Won: Teaser~
JinSoul: It's 12:17~
JinSoul: The teaser was released~
JinSoul: I guess the beat of the song is fastest among all the girl groups
Go Won: Right~ Super exciting song~
(Now everyone knows about what they're talking about!)
Kim Lip: High~
Kim Lip: You might be shocked~